[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Thank you for calling.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Passmart Customer.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Karen, this is Heather.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Can I get your first and last name, please?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Speaker 2: Tiffany Stacey.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Thank you, Stacey.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And can you verify your email and phone number for me?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: TiffScafe at gmail.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And my phone number is 647-406-8201.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Perfect.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you so much.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: And how can I help you tonight?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I'm just trying to put in an order online and I have an associate discount.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And it's still see double discount days, but it's just not going through.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: So your orders are not going through, or the discount's not working?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: The discount's only doing regular discount instead of the double.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Let's check it out.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You just have that one singular account, not like two different ones, possibly.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I think I have one.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is everything in your basket that you need to?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Oh, wait, I'm in the wrong application.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I need to go into Canada.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: It is totally loading your basket.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I think it's because you have it on the auto ship, possibly.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I do.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] I have the, like I looked into it at work and it's close to stack.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Let me see if I can find something on that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You said it's a double discount day for associates, right?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Double turn.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Just one minute, please.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Hi, Stephanie.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Are you still with me?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So I can't do anything tonight, but what I could do for you is submit a ticket if you like.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: So do I just put through the order now anyways, and then the ticket will help me with getting with the other 15% back?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I believe so.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Are you a bandfield associate or a normal associate for PetSmart?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: I work in the salon.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: So double discount not working.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, let's see.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] What's your store location?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 3204.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: That's the Toronto Liberty store?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Let's see.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Let me create the ticket while I'm on the phone in case I have to ask any questions.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I don't know.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, I just do the order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Could you you just submitted your order?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yep.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: And it was just an extra 15%?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Do you have a picture you can send up the 15% discount?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I'm just going to manually honor it into a ticket because I'm having problems submitting the ticket right now.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Please submit.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 15% of the count.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Let's see.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: So what I have like in terms of the 15% is the associate double discount days and then the information which says that it stacks with the first authorship order and it's good until November 2nd.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And then the order is on my XL like the order details.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So it shows how much I got off and it will add up to about 50% instead of 65%.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] All the information you need, like do you need me to send you a screenshot of the order details or just that thing that says the associate discount?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I would say just all of it just for record.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, sounds good.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] And where do I send that to?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: I think I just sent you an email.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Did I?
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Yeah.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] It just sent.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, perfect.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, so I'm going to reply to that right now with the order details and the associate double discount.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] There was also like an SAQ which reiterated that it would stack.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] So I'll add that there.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: Okay, I did the additional 15% off.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So you'll receive a refund.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It could be immediate.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It could take up to seven business days.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Bye.
[unknown] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: So you won't get like a receipt from me, but it'll be notated in the account.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] 2: Okay, perfect.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Okay, great.
[speaker_SPEAKER_01] Have a good night.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] 1: You too.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Bye.